I'm back.
I apologize.
I made it.
What's up?
Oh my
god.
Okay, let me just turn this down a bit.
I had to go to the apothecary real quick before they closed.
I had to get something for the doctor tomorrow and it's really early tomorrow so this was the last call.
I thought about it the moment after I started stream.
I knew I had forgotten something today, but that was it.
I made it though.
Yeah, everything's fine.
What are you unlocking as Hazel 5?
Today!
We're going through three, four, five today.
Bang, bang, bang.
One after the other.
Yep, yep.
I hope you enjoyed the Starcraft music while it was gone.
And maybe I should have put Jackie on instead.
She could have entertained you while I was gone.
She's expressed interest in the game Stray.
She really wants to stream that apparently.
Maybe I'll let her do it at some point.
Okay, good.
Face your fears, play Bethany.
You're right!
I did promise that.
Look at this.
Remember Bethany?
She's calling.
Megastan ending?
I'm not sure what that means.
I have no idea why I wrote that.
There's also something else I wrote.
What was it?
I think that was about it.
Yeah, actually maybe I'll do this under the line like that.
Same over here.
Secret room like that.
Boom.
We're doing Bethany today.
We're doing her.
Are you excited?
We're also gonna do... There was one other one that I wanted to do.
I forgot what it was.
It was Bethany and what else guys?
I promised something else last time.
Greed mode, I think.
Yes, I think you're right.
Stream just crashed for you?
Oh shit.
Hello, hello, hello.
Can you hear me?
Don't do the Bethany.
Oh, now I will definitely do her.
It's fine.
For me, it's fine.
Okay, okay.
Pause alarm.
Are you sure you want to do greed mode?
I think so.
One sec.
And there it is.
I apologize to the people who went to take a break counting on the timer.
I'm starting one minute early.
Well, I can't really say that after I'm already 20 minutes late.
But yeah, no.
Let's do this.
I'm ready.
Okay, this is check.
Drinks or check.
Mousepad out of the way.
Fan is turned on.
Check.
Arm turned on.
Let's do this.
We're gonna go Bethany.
The book of virtues.
Hey, at least the win streak isn't negative, right?
That's a good sign.
Okay, I need to remember how how she works.
So we have this active item that is for some reason not in my inventory.
Why not?
It's so weird.
Anyway, when I use it, I get a little fly.
And now I have two flies.
And I can combine it with other items.
And we currently have Curse of Lost.
I wonder though, if I walk through here, will it consume a fly?
It will not.
Copy's head.
More flies for me.
Wait, item spawn.
Oh, hold on a minute.
This is gonna combine with my current.
Outer Wisp.
1 HP.
1.5 damage.
Item spawns wisps instead of flies.
Oh, that's pretty good, I guess.
Spawns a blue fly on death.
Sick!
Look at all these flies I have!
Okay, that's actually kind of dope.
Not bad.
I gotta get into Bethany mode here.
Or Isaac mode, I guess.
Keep it.
Dude, I have a whole solo system.
This is the real solo system.
Oh no!
They're absorbing shots.
Nice.
A buffer this early?
It's kind of nice.
Dead bird.
Activates only when Isaac takes damage.
When active, chases and damages enemies.
Right.
I could actually get in there without taking damage.
It may not be worth it.
I'm gonna take damage.
Wait a minute!
Oh, I don't have a buffer!
Because the blue hearts go into the blue heart thingy instead.
Right.
Oh wait, I'm using blue hearts when I do that.
Of course.
I think I've remembered how to do this now, guys.
It's okay.
Don't worry, I'm not rage baiting.
This is just the start, okay?
It's gonna get worse.
Wait, am I shooting extra?
Wait a second!
I'm shooting extra attacks!
When I have these... Look at that!
It's like a whole ass rain.
It's not hitting anything, though.
Is it?
Oh, it is, it is.
It's just not a lot of damage.
No, stop!
Stop that!
Stop it!
He just took like four of my flies.
Okay, another bomb is good.
I'm saving my flies for the bosses and stuff.
Dude, this is actually kind of cool.
I dig it.
The other one is paid to win.
Oh my goodness.
What's that?
Filigree feather?
Let's just spot one of these before I forget.
Defeated angels will drop angel room items instead of key...
Whoa!
Okay, we got a step today!
If a key piece was... Oh, that also means we got to do angels.
No demons.
If a key piece was previously collected, angels will spawn the other key piece.
Got it.
Wait, so that means right now I cannot get any key pieces, because it's always going to be angel pieces now.
Or I guess angel items.
This is the real solar system!
More like the asteroid belt.
Wait, is there an upper limit of the amount of flies I can have?
I feel like I just didn't get any new ones there.
I think there may be.
Oh, oh, look at that!
Black hearts!
Oh, they don't count either.
So there's actually a big disadvantage to playing Bethany.
You can't really have a buffer.
Well, you could say these flies count as buffers, but you know, it's not quite the same.
Oh, nice!
Not gonna matter here, because I can see the whole map.
Steven!
Look at how much knockback I have!
At least on the small guy.
Nice!
Homing tears?
I'll take it.
Spawn one more fly.
I don't think I'm done here.
Okay, I will say guys, so far Bethany's kind of cool.
I will admit it.
I think I came from here.
Yeah.
Nice.
Dude, I feel like the guppy item I got is kind of crazy for Bethany.
I get to spawn one of these after every room now.
Not bad.
I don't think I've been this way, yeah.
Lust!
Insane DPS as well.
Nice!
HP up.
I don't see what was down.
Oh, lockdown, I guess?
Probably.
Good one.
I have one bomb left.
I could try and look for a secret room, but
nah.
Not when I can't see the map.
The sun ain't gonna help me either here.
Moving on.
Oh, wait, we got healing.
Now we really need to be careful, because we have no real buffer.
We have the fake buffer.
We have a buffer.
Okay, focus.
This is when everything matters.
Kind of want to go in there, but not when I don't have full HP.
Dude, kind of kill it.
Oh, nice!
Open up the rock for me there.
I'm not gonna use a bomb yet.
Let's just remember we can come back.
I could use the sun here.
Let's just reveal all the secret rooms.
You know what I could do?
I could walk into the curse room and put on the sun.
I'm gonna do it.
This is genius.
What was that?
Oh, it was flies.
Okay.
Uh, we're gonna do this.
We're gonna go back, and now we're gonna use the sun.
Reveal the rest of the map.
Full HP.
Not bad, eh?
Also, wait a minute!
We have a 100% angel chance.
I think I remember having realized that before on her, but that's apparently a thing.
Not bad.
More blue hearts.
Why not?
I was almost about to bomb that wall, looking for a secret room until I realized that would have been a mistake.
Holy shit!
Dude, that was close!
What the heck?
Yeah, there's definitely an upper limit on how many of these you can have.
Right?
Let me check.
No, actually, I think that spawned another one.
That actually did spawn another one just now.
That was my last bomb.
What's that?
R-Key.
R-Key is consumed to restart the run, sending Isaac back to the first floor, but with all of the collected items.
Whoa!
What?
Wait, that's crazy.
But are the floors regenerated then?
Hold on a minute.
I feel like this is better.
Am I crazy?
I wonder if I leave this here, if I use the R-Key now, I go back, start over, I come back and collect Guppy's head again.
I feel like Guppy's head is better.
Like, I don't want to go back.
This is a great run so far.
Am I nuts?
Maybe I'm nuts.
Maybe I'll change my mind.
We'll see.
If shit hits the fan and we really fuck up here, then I'll go back.
This is the plan.
What's that?
Proptosis.
Tears gain a large damage bonus, but have much shorter range.
Much shorter range.
That's not a lot of extra damage.
I'm taking it.
That's fine.
It's totally cool.
It's not even that bad.
That did not spawn an extra fly, unfortunately.
Also, they're not called flies.
Wisps, right?
Wisps.
I
have 22 gold.
Ooh, that's also cool.
X1 middle wisp, 1 HP.
I don't know what that means.
What does that mean?
Times one middle wisp.
1-8.
Wait, I need to see my current one again.
Outer wisp.
Oh, wait, I think I understand.
So, middle wisp is something that is closer to my body.
So, if I were to take this hourglass, I wouldn't be spawning a ring of wisps all the way out where I have them now.
They would be spawning in a tighter ring, I guess.
Wisps lost in the previous room are restored.
That's kind of crazy.
It's only when you use it, I guess.
Right.
I may have to... You know what?
I'm gonna donate.
I got so much money, uh, we gotta start donating.
Max donation, man.
We're making progress today.
One way or the other.
Even if this run turns to shit, at least we'll have done something.
You know?
I think it's smart.
I see you up there.
Whoa!
He can crawl through that little crack.
Okay, here we go.
The heart.
We cannot take damage now.
We cannot take damage.
Look at the knockback I have on him.
Dude, that's crazy.
The laser would kill me.
But let's not get hit by the laser.
Dude, look at that!
Look at the knockback!
Wow!
That was crazy.
Uh, more tears is nice.
An angel as well.
Uh, the wafer.
Amazing.
Yes.
Ah, wait, I shouldn't have taken that yet.
I should have taken that after, uh, we had this fight.
That was bad.
Wait, I don't have a bomb.
I can't...
Oh no!
I cannot engage the angel!
No!
Wait, wait, maybe I can come back.
I can't come back!
Ah, shit.
Okay, I feel like we should try the archae then.
Maybe we can come back.
I hope the actual floors are gonna be the same.
Um, where was it?
Down here.
I'm so scared.
Please don't fuck this up.
Please don't.
Is it gonna revert the donation I made?
We'll find out, I guess.
Here we go.
Okay, looks like we still have the curse of lost.
Uh, right.
Go in here.
Oh, it's different!
Oh, actually, maybe that's good.
That means I'm gonna have the potential to have even more items.
Okay, so it's actually not the same.
Yeah, this is... Oh, we can step!
Angel dreams are restored, maybe.
Also, we should be using that.
Uh, yeah, let's not take any damage here.
Even though it's not the floor where taking damage is gonna matter too much, you know.
Yeah, we need bombs.
We need it now.
Oh, that's really good as well.
I feel like we should save up for that.
I guess Bethany's all about the active, right?
That's like her whole shtick.
Wait, actually, yeah, let's just do the boss now.
There we go.
It's Widow.
Okay, that was easy.
Nailed him.
We got two hearts here.
We're gonna save one of them.
Nice.
I'll be back.
This is a good step towards stepping.
4.43 damage is also solid.
We're not gonna step just yet.
We're gonna wait just a bit.
Just wanna fly.
I kind of miss Gopi's head, though.
I will say that.
Umbilical cord.
Entering a room with half a red heart or less.
Gaining a little Steven familiar.
Oh, I already have one.
30% chance of taking damage to spawn a Gemini.
Okay, okay, fine.
Oh, wait, it replaces it.
Um, no, then I'll take this.
I want to do the angel thing.
Don't waste the wisps unnecessarily here.
Okay, what do we got here?
Whoa!
All right!
Wait, how does that work, then?
X1 middle wisp.
4 HP.
3 damage?
Hmm, interesting.
The problem is, though, I can't really spawn wisps very often now.
This is like the issue.
I don't like this room.
I'm leaving.
Yeah.
Man, uh... I guess we go step.
Wait a bit.
Is there more?
Almost down here.
That's not a pedestal item.
It's not gonna work.
I think we just start stepping a little bit.
Okay, I'll come back.
I need to get the 2 HP.
Oh,
I could also do... No, no, I'm gonna save my bomb.
Save the bomb.
Oh, man, I, um... Nah, nah, nah, nah.
Go back.
Maybe we'll get like a million coins spawning.
That would be amazing.
Okay, three coins is nice.
Oh, yes!
Uh, wait, uh, that's the Bible.
Wait, I can re-roll in here.
Oh, wait a minute.
This is pretty good, though.
I mean, that one is pretty good.
What is that one again?
We charge us one bar of Isaac's active item each time he takes damage.
Not that great.
The Bible... 3 HP 6 damage.
Wait, homing tears.
Holy shit.
I think I'm gonna re-roll, man.
Wait, what?
What's happening?
Uh, okay.
We have, uh... Oh, we have D6?
Wisps now.
Interesting.
I don't know what's happening right now.
Replaces tears with large piercing burst.
That's also good.
I like that one.
Circle of protection.
Creates a ring around Isaac that has a chance to reflect enemy protect.
Okay, that's not super cool.
Mitre, 33% chance of quoting red heart drops.
That's also good.
We don't know what this is.
I kind of want to try that.
Dead dove.
Flight and... FLIGHT!
And spectral tears!
That's amazing.
I'm glad I took the chance on that.
Okay, we're gonna bomb this guy.
I'm so happy I saved my bomb.
I'm so happy.
This guy ain't nothing.
Hey, hey, what's that?
Act of contrition.
More tears.
Eternal heart allows angel rooms to appear even if a devil room has been taken.
Yield chance reduction is decreased.
What?
Guess we'll find out.
I'm curious.
Uh, I'm not gonna step anymore because I have an eternal heart now.
We gotta move on.
That was good.
That was nice.
Very nice.
And then again, if I keep stepping, it's gonna spawn another angel, man.
Oh, do I do I pass up this?
Oh, that's such a crazy decision.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna not do it.
We're not doing it.
We're moving on.
Holy shit.
This run is so exciting.
This is amazing.
Okay, we got this room.
Uh, I guess I can enter.
Oh wait, that's actually a thing here.
Yeah, we can enter without... Ah.
At least that doesn't reduce my deal chance.
Wait, is that what that meant?
Hold on.
Yield chance reduction is decreased.
Oh, maybe that means when I take damage it's not as punishing.
Maybe that's what that means.
Because, I mean, why would I have a lesser deal chance?
That's bad, right?
Oh, yeah, I can fly now.
This one.
Step away from me.
ANSUS!
Amazing.
I hate that.
We're gonna re-roll it.
Uh, that's gonna take us to two out of three and conjoined.
I think I like it.
Wait a minute, can I re-roll 18 times?
Because I... it's gonna consume blue hearts.
Holy shit.
Dude, this build is broken.
This is wild.
Uh, hold on, I gotta...
Delete this.
There we go.
Gotta blow this up.
Wow, what a chest!
Insanity.
Oh, my d6s are shooting red projectiles, too.
More keys.
Dude, Bethany's awesome.
Alright, guys, Bethany's awesome.
I said it.
This is indeed awesome.
It's cool.
I'll take that.
We can also re-roll in here.
Uh, wow, upon purchasing a new item immediately, it takes its place.
That's actually kind of good.
I think I'll maybe save for that.
We're not gonna waste any flies.
I mean, wisps.
Oh, here.
Oh, my god.
That's 15 coins.
We're taking the restock thingy.
I could also re-roll.
Ooh, hold on now.
Ah, but re-rolling this is kind of a waste, because there's only two items.
I'm taking this.
Yeah, the restock is just fantastic.
Imagine I have, like, a million gold suddenly, and I find a shop that sells blue hearts, right?
How crazy would that be?
Two red hearts?
That's also kind of good.
Okay, we can't take damage now.
You're gonna charge me?
Wow, my damage is crazy.
Uh, I could re-roll this.
Because, oh, actually, no, it's good for me, because I cannot pick up blue hearts anyway.
So, Bethany is all about red hearts.
I want this.
Uh, Pachal candle?
It's a stacking tears bonus for each room cleared without taking damage up to a maximum of plus...
That's pretty good as well, but, uh, I kind of want to re-roll.
Holy water is also kind of... I'm gonna re-roll again!
Oh, shit!
Wait, I lost, like, a shit ton of blue hearts.
I think it's for every level of charge.
I see.
I'm taking this.
No, it's an active!
Delirious?
Summons delirium in a random boss form to fight for Isaac.
Delirium lasts until destroyed from taking enough damage.
Only one delirium summon can be active at a time and its health deteriorates over time.
What the fuck?
Look how many charges it has!
Ah, that's kind of bad for someone like Bethany who wants to use her charges.
I'm going to take this and come back and re-roll when I have enough charges again.
Also, we're going to blow this guy up, of course.
We're going to put it right here.
Oh, wait, I can't come back!
Oh, no!
Maybe I have to re-roll again.
Okay.
What the hell is that?
Is that the mini version of the same item?
I'm going to have to try it.
Little Delirium!
You're kidding me.
Conjoined!
Familia that mimics the forms and attacks of many other familiars.
Shifts to a new form every 10 seconds.
Okay.
Well, look at all these projectiles now.
That's awesome.
Kind of feel like I should take this now just for fun, right?
But the D6, man.
The D6 is just... it's goated.
I got to take the D6.
We're not done here.
We're not done.
I'm going to go to the treasure room down here.
Well, it's not really a treasure room.
It's like a chest room, I guess.
Nice.
Two keys needed here.
Shit!
Oh, well.
Our lock had to stop at some point.
Okay, some money is good.
Don't want to say that was worth it, though, coming back for this, but...
I mean, it was in the sense that it's just free items, right?
No, actually not, because we did get a range down.
I think that was not worth it.
There's a bomb here.
I could do this humbling bundle.
Oh, no, I don't have enough unless I...
I kind of want to get that as well.
Is that crazy?
Do we have any leftover coins somewhere?
Maybe this guy?
Shit.
Ah, whatever.
Let's go.
Let's go to the boss.
I could try and blow up these.
I have five bombs.
Let's do it.
Am I good or what?
Am I the greatest?
Is it me?
My reflection?
Seven damage?
Oh, this is the one where it comes back.
I think it may be okay.
Yeah, because they disappear anyway, guys.
Look, they're not coming back.
That is so good.
Unbelievable.
Okay, now we go.
Now we go.
This is going wild.
By the way, my plans are we are going to go home.
We're going to find a teleporter card and we're going to...
I'm going to unlock, okay?
This is the plan.
Holy shit.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
There we go.
A pill!
No!
But I guess it's fair.
We've gotten pretty lucky so far.
It had to catch up to us at some point.
Faded Polaroid.
That's cool.
But do I want to replace my thingy with it, though?
Yeah, maybe not.
Oh, actually, that's a guaranteed open door, then.
Maybe I will keep it, depending on what we find.
Another health down, no thanks.
If this floor has a stepping room, I'm going to come back here for the filigree feather.
That's the plan.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
20 gold as well.
No, that's, no!
Rip my angels.
Wish me luck on angels.
I really need it.
Man, the pushback I have is nuts.
Wait, I have this little bastard.
I forgot his name.
Stuy increases, oh, more range?
Yeah, oh, I walked into that.
I think that's good, actually.
I want that.
I'm not going to re-roll it.
Wait, did that make it worse?
Why do I feel like my range got less from that?
Are you kidding me?
What the fuck is that crap?
I definitely don't have more range.
Maybe it's like, because I have the reflection thing, it's actually decreasing range?
Fuck, man, I...
Well, today I learned.
Damn, that's crazy.
Definitely here.
Yep.
Oh, we're going to be bombing this.
I need pills.
Only one pill.
Okay, experimental, let's see.
Range up.
No!
Oh, wait, now it does feel like my range is better.
I don't understand how that works.
Also, let me just confirm this Polaroid thing.
Can we use to open a strange door?
Yeah, yeah, okay.
Um, let's go.
I need to find a treasure room and re-roll.
This is the plan.
Wait, maybe I want range down.
If I find a pill that gives range down, that's good for me.
Also, call me crazy, but it said plus seven damage before.
And I only have six right now.
How does that work?
I feel like I should have way more damage.
This run is confusing me.
I am very confused.
Here we go.
Oh, wait, do I want this?
I think I want this.
But wait, is that going to fuck up my conjoined?
That's actually, that's actually bad for me.
Because the conjoined shoots in three directions.
This thing is going to collapse it all into one.
It's not good for me.
I'm going to re-roll it.
That's horrible.
We're going to re-roll again when we have energy.
If we can even get the energy.
Dude, I think I just donate everything.
No, no, wait, wait.
We're going to keep exploring and then donate.
Go up here.
Man, I hope I can find my...
What's the word?
The little guppy, the little guppy active.
I want that back.
I've had enough of the D6.
Oh, wait, how does that work?
Hold on a minute.
Okay, so we can take a devil deal and still be good, I guess.
I don't want to re-roll, man, when, when I'm using my blue hearts for it.
I want to re-roll with only green energy.
No, this is...
Okay, fine.
I'll do it.
Guppy's paw.
Wait, X3 middle wisp.
20 HP, that's a lot.
3.5 damage.
I'm going to take this just to get two out of three on guppy.
I'm kind of curious about it.
I'm going to take that and I'll come back.
When I say come back, I mean, I never come back.
Okay, 25 coins.
Was there anything in the shop?
Let me see.
Anything I wanted?
Nah, I'm going to donate all.
Until it breaks.
Oh, nice.
Didn't break yet.
669.
Delicious.
We're leaving.
Oh wait, I can fly.
I don't have to dodge that.
Thank you.
We are getting out of here.
Wait, that's not the way out of here.
Let's cycle.
We also have the lovers.
Don't really care about that.
Level four.
Well, it's technically level seven or so, really.
Because we went back, right?
That's kind of crazy, actually, that we did that.
Okay, we cannot take damage now.
We really have to focus now.
Oh, god.
Okay, this.
Dude, all these pills have sucked for me.
I do not have good pill luck.
I am so slow right now.
Notice how fast these guys are dying, and they usually have a lot of HP.
That is impressive.
I could go in there, but not yet.
Dodge that.
This guy's going to appear there.
Wait, I have spectral tears, dude.
I can just hide in the rocks.
Of course.
We also have a full charge now.
Ah, but we don't know what it is, so we're just going to take it.
Monstro's tooth.
Why not?
Right, that's what that does.
I'll be back.
Did I just lose demon?
Oh, nice.
Wow.
Latchkey.
What else did that one do?
Lock and...
That's so hard, okay.
Sweet.
I'm slowly losing my familiars here, or my little wisps.
It's not good.
I think I destroyed a black poop.
Okay, let's do the boss without taking damage.
Come on, baby.
Vistula, this is actually a better boss for me.
I've got good AOE.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, that's amazing!
Blood clot damage and range up, sure.
Yeah, my range is literally getting smaller.
The more I...
Wait, why am I shooting?
Oh, the blood clot, I guess.
Oh, I can't see what things are.
Ah, this is not great, man.
I guess I'll just take one.
Breath of Life.
Oh, that one, that's actually kind of cool.
Oh, this is really good for her!
Guys, it's a one-charge item!
Holding used...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, this is great!
This is actually amazing.
Are we gonna kill this guy to get another item?
Wow, that...
He died fast.
Key piece two.
Wait, I had a key piece?
Oh, I didn't have the trinket!
I guess I left it behind, didn't I?
That's fine.
It is what...
Let me try this again.
Wait, did that spawn up?
Oh.
Oh!
Okay, I see.
Well, in that case, then I don't want it.
I thought it was gonna spawn one of those every time.
Blood of the Martyr.
Sure.
I mean...
It is what it is.
I can't really take it back, you know?
We're leaving.
Let's keep exploring.
That was solid, man.
Like, this is going great.
More damage is good.
I want to go to the curse room.
Okay, that was a very boring one.
The wafer is gonna be so sick, by the way.
The wafer may actually be one of the best items in the game.
Simply because of how much damage is gonna negate, especially late game.
Let's head this way.
Doorstop.
This one is also very good.
The fact that you can just nope out.
You can kind of scope out a room, you know?
And see, okay, how bad is it?
Oh, it's bad.
We go back out and plan a strategy, right?
But I'm keeping the Polaroid.
Okay.
Only three coins?
Ah, okay, nice.
Now I like to see this when there's no shop anyway.
Okay,
only three bombs.
Let's check the fight club.
See if it's open.
There's no step room.
It's closed, okay.
All right, we're done here.
Moving on.
Dude, what if you find another R key?
Can you just go again and again and again and again?
Imagine.
Imagine that.
Just go back again and again and again and again.
Also, you know what I could have done?
I just realized.
What if I had picked up the R key?
Kept going until almost the very end, until things were looking bleak and then started over.
That would have maybe been even better.
I kind of regret doing it early now.
Oh, lucky.
Oh, shit.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I forgot which floor we're on.
Come on, Mom.
Okay.
Chance to add additional pickups.
No, no, no.
I guess I could...
No, this is not a pedestal item.
No rerolling.
They're all like stunned.
The hell is that?
Oh, it's mine, okay.
Really?
I call bullshit on that.
That's BS.
Didn't even have a chance to react to that.
That was like instantaneous.
Nice.
We have 16 blue balls now.
Nothing better than a bunch of blue balls.
Thank you.
I want to find answers.
Or maybe a sun.
Why is Mom in every room?
Leave me alone, Mom.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna blow that up.
I have no faith.
What?
Oh, my goodness.
All my freaking wisps are going to go away.
Free lemonade.
Spawns a large pool of damaging yellow creep.
Reroll.
Stop giving me actives.
Unless it's the guppy active.
Just eight additional contact damage.
Boo, man.
I'll be back with more energy.
I'm not going to consume my blue hearts on that shit.
I only reroll with green energy.
I think about the environment.
Green energy only.
Thank you.
Just go behind it.
What's this?
No problem.
Gym.
Really got to be careful in rooms like this.
Harkalas!
Interesting.
It's not answers, but you know.
It's something.
Ventricle razor.
I've yet to find a good use for that.
Boss is here.
Uh, I'm a little afraid of that boss, because it might be mom.
I didn't really keep track of what floor I'm on.
So I'm going to play it safe and just explore a bit more first.
And try and look for a secret room as well.
I think I may have a couple of candidates here.
It's not this one.
Let's see, could be in here.
Could be right there.
Looking good so far.
Oh, looking very good, actually.
Shit.
Uh, could be here.
Okay, I know.
Here.
Okay, good.
No, not this guy.
I've got so much money now.
I keep forgetting what's at the shop.
Oh, there's nothing at the shop, because the guy was there.
Uh, let's go back and re-roll.
We have energy now.
That's what I wanted to do.
What's that?
Lil Spewer, puking buddy.
Charges and releases puke attacks that create creep with different effects.
Familius form and creep attack change each time Isaac consumes a pill.
Huh.
I see.
Can I see what he's doing now?
I'm just going to eat pills.
Hey, okay.
Let's find a room where we can destroy some stuff.
Like a big room.
A lot of breakables.
Maybe this one.
Yeah.
Nothing.
Okay.
Too bad.
I'm going to get the lovers, and we're going to leave.
Worst case, I can use my blue energy on the boss.
To re-roll things.
But if I get a health up, I'm taking it.
Oh my god, you bastard.
You do that attack, don't you?
Nice, we take that.
Angel!
That's actually pretty good.
I may take it.
Yeah, I like.
Oh, you fucker.
Oh my god!
So wait, what happens if I kill angels after I get both key pieces?
Maybe they just naturally start to give me angel items.
I'm going to step first chance I get.
Uh, keep...
Did we miss something?
We got the lovers.
Check, check.
Yeah, we're good.
Okay, now it's mom.
We can actually enter now if we want to.
I'm not going to do it though.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let me think.
Yeah, this is good.
We're going to get bookworm.
Telepathy for dummies.
Gain homing tears.
Use it.
Just to spawn a wisp.
Necromonicon.
Instant damage to everyone.
Yo, I could actually re-roll in here.
I could re-roll these and potentially get the...
the one that gives me blue hearts, which is kind of crazy.
I'll think about it.
This is so exciting.
Oh, a stepping room!
We're going to try the angel thing.
Uh, but we're not going to step yet.
We're going to wait and see how much extra HP we're going to get.
Yeah, this is very exciting.
Right for experimentation here.
Okay, we got a shop now.
Oh, duplicate of...
That's actually interesting.
I am reaching the point where I may not want to carry around the d6 anymore.
This could be really good.
You know?
Let's keep that in mind.
I want to keep my options open.
Oh, dude.
The world!
Yes!
The world.
Sick!
And we have pills as well.
Three blue flies.
Friends till the end.
I'll take that.
I'm going to go in here.
Technology zero.
Tears have small beams of electricity that arc between them.
Dude, I love this.
And they arc between them because it's conjoined?
Guys.
Guys, this is actually...
I didn't even think about that.
I thought it was just, you know...
Yeah, I don't know what I thought, actually.
I thought it would still be good, but not that good.
We are totally cooking right now.
Can you smell that?
That's delicious meals.
Bombs.
How about that?
Soul hearts!
Yes, sir.
The hierophant.
Gimme.
We even have a battery here for later.
I'm actually going to destroy this guy.
We're going to get angel chance from it.
Heh heh.
Yo, I did spectral tears as well.
This is crazy.
Now we just need some more actual range, not the fake range.
If we can get that, then we're totally skating.
Less speed.
No, thanks.
Hakodas would have been fun in there.
Who's making that sound?
All the time.
Okay.
Boss?
Where the hell are you?
Here's the boss.
Uhhh...
Wait a minute.
Hold up.
I can't go in there.
I just realized.
If I go in, I can't get out.
The Polaroid is not going to help me then.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
Wait a minute.
Uhhh...
Okay, I guess we can just enter now without...
But that's so sad.
Maybe I'll step first?
We also have the curse room.
Fuckin' hell.
Please.
Gimme like a crazy card.
Dammit.
We gotta look for more secrets.
Also, what was in the shop?
I forgot.
Oh, we could do this.
This is gonna spawn cards, right?
Maybe we get a fool card.
Worst case, we're gonna get a lot of hearts we can use to step.
If I'm lucky.
Oh, actually, maybe it's the other machine that gives cards.
The tarot reading machine.
And what makes sense?
Tarot cards, right?
Yeah, what's with my lock?
Dude, are you kidding me?
Okay, destroy it.
Get my bomb back, at least.
So we have one, two, two and a half hearts.
And we're only gonna take one half a heart of damage.
From stepping.
Right?
Yeah.
What's that?
Chances spawn a dead bird familiar each time you kill an enemy.
Uh, no.
Okay, some healing is good.
That's two more steps.
Ooh.
Uh-oh.
I had to push them away.
Oh, here we go!
Angel item!
Wow, he died fast!
Nothing.
You gotta be shitting me.
Okay.
Well, maybe that wasn't worth it then.
Whatever.
Kind of feels bad that I have all these...
all this energy on my d6, you know?
And there's nothing I have been wanting to use it on, even.
Oh, wait, a library!
We gotta go back to the library and use it there.
That's one thing I want to do.
Also, we could do this.
Maybe I'll exchange this before I leave, actually.
Could I just donate the rest of my money?
Yeah, no, wait, wait, let me think.
Back to the library first.
We're gonna use the d6.
I'm trying to think what item I would want from the library.
I don't think all the books spawn in there.
Some books only spawn in, like, the demon rooms and shit, right?
So...
Let's try.
Book of shadows.
Damage nullifying shield.
Revelations!
No way!
Uh, six charges for that one.
Could be good, I guess.
I could also take this first and then use it.
Just to get at that little familiar.
Take this one.
24 hearts now, blue hearts, by the way.
I could re-roll this again.
Maybe not worth it.
So the d6, there's no other items I need to re-roll, right?
Let me think.
No.
I think we're good on that.
Oh, wait a sec!
Book of revelations.
I think if I have to choose, I would rather take the one that duplicates my familiars.
For an active, yeah.
I guess I could also go to the shop and re-roll.
But that's really risky.
I could get something really bad.
You know?
Fuck, this is such a tough choice, guys.
I could also take this, use it, and then re-roll it.
Obviously, it's only gonna be for the current room, but it's just to get the little wisp, right?
Wouldn't be the worst idea.
But then if I re-roll, I only have eight coins left.
I won't be able to buy anything meaningful.
So, you know what?
I'm actually gonna...
I'm gonna keep my d6 for now.
Yeah.
I'll just hang on to it.
I think it's okay.
We're gonna grab this battery.
We're gonna grab the hearts that I'm missing.
We also have the lovers.
Let's not forget that.
The lovers is actually extra good, because we have the wafer.
So, every heart means so much more.
Don't go in!
I almost went in.
Jesus Christ.
Bad boy, bad boy!
Imagine this didn't even work.
Imagine I misread my Polaroid thingy.
Oh, wait, it got consumed!
Oh, wait, uh, maybe I go back and grab...
Wasn't there another trinket?
Ayy!
Ah, why not?
We can even do some more stepping.
Whoa!
What the fuck?
Oh, you wanna die?
You wanna die, bitch?
Still no item for me.
I'm gonna keep stepping, fuck it.
Oh, no.
Wait, this may be bad for me!
Can I come back?
No!
I don't wanna do this!
I messed up!
I don't like any of these.
Uh, blocks, enemy shots is good.
Enemy, blue, no, I guess I'll take this.
Fuck me, dude.
Oh my god, I need to remember that that can happen in there.
No!
Oh, well, this is actually okay.
I mean, honestly, at this point, I don't even know what I'm gonna get, you know?
Like, I guess I can unlock the other version of Bethany if I had gone the other way.
But this way, maybe I'll get something even better that I don't even know, right?
This is the thing.
Oh, wait, I could have rerolled those items, actually, if I wanted to.
I should have rerolled them, man.
Wait, I can go back and reroll them, still.
Let me go back.
Oh, shit!
Uh, what's that?
Shard of glass.
Can't just spawn a red heart when damaged.
That's really good!
Imagine that!
With wafer.
Taking damage will make Isaac gush blood tears.
Every 20 seconds, well, oh, okay, wait, I don't like that.
No, I don't like that.
That's terrible.
Key bomb.
No.
Upon entering each room, Isaac becomes camouflaged, confusing enemies and preventing them from attacking.
Okay, brief moment.
Camouflage is...
No.
Sci-fly, I don't even want to look at the others.
We're taking that, baby.
Totally worth.
Okay, it's not going to help me against lasers.
Sci-fly, when will you learn to block lasers?
I will say, though, I don't think my damage is that good.
Could be better.
Wow.
Wait, why is there an arrow up here?
Oh, it's a key?
Is that what that symbol means?
I guess so.
I can still use my d6.
Wow.
Stay at an angle.
Nice.
What the fuck is this?
That's got to be something to do with that.
Like, look at that.
Something's going on with that.
Hold on, I'm going to take a picture of this.
This...
I've seen this before.
I know there's something about that.
There's something about this.
That's way too conspicuous.
Oh, almost ran into that.
Yeah, my damage is not great, man.
Boss?
Not yet.
Wait, also, what the fuck?
There's a boss here.
But there's also the door.
I honestly forget where those paths lead.
I don't remember.
I have no idea where this leads.
No clue.
It's just one of a million other bosses, you know?
You're not dead.
Two soul hearts?
I should probably save my bombs.
I only have two.
Look at these Siemens.
Or sperm.
Little toad stools, or whatever they're called.
Tadpoles?
Toadpoles?
I...
What is the fucking name for those?
You know what I mean.
Little swimmers.
Maybe that's what's happening, you know?
So we go into the womb at some point, and then the uterus.
And if we go deep enough, we're actually at the inception stage, where the sperm is gonna go to the egg.
Before Isaac is even born.
Think about it.
It makes sense.
Push it away.
Go down here.
Yeah, my damage against these guys is bad.
Oh, nevermind, it's actually pretty good.
Sci-fly is gonna be so good, guys.
Sci-fly plus wafer?
Man, I'm gonna feel really comfortable during boss fights, even though I only have five hearts.
Five hearts is like 10 hearts right now for me.
I'm so scared.
Okay, we've cleared everything.
I'm gonna go do the boss icon, and then we're gonna go do the door afterwards, if I can.
I don't remember if one excludes the other.
I have no fucking clue.
We'll see.
I'm taking a gamble here.
The lamb!
Oh, okay.
All right, he spawned a little piece of shit as well.
Oh, shit.
Oh, he's dead.
Little P.O.S.
is dead.
No!
No victory lap!
Wait, I can also go down?
Oh my god, I'm so confused.
Wait, no!
I didn't mean to do that.
It finally happened.
Well, alabaster box has appeared.
At least we unlocked something.
Man, what a disaster.
Oh well.
But guys, we learned a lot.
The first thing we learned, Bethany kind of rocks.
So much so that I kind of want to do it again.
Also, look at that little achievement we got on her.
The box in the center.
That's the only thing we did on Bethany.
I kind of want to do Yulith.
Let's go.
We're going to do greed after.
That's when I change things up a little bit.
Um, don't go in there yet.
Nice.
Good start.
Why is the store closed?
Oh, because we didn't like that, I guess.
Let's see what we got in here.
Boo!
Let me think.
Yeah, boo.
Terrible item.
Man, terrible.
Is that a ham?
So to get in there, I need a bomb and a key.
Got it.
Watch me not get either.
Oh yeah, oh man.
It's so awkward having my familiar shoot.
I gotta get used to that again.
Shit.
Uh, no.
A bomb.
Good.
Now we need a key.
Can we get it?
That's scary.
I can buy a key, maybe, if I have enough gold.
Dude, this shop has a shit ton of items.
That because I upgraded it so much.
That's kind of nuts.
Wow.
Either that or I just got insanely lucky.
Oh, that was close.
Oh, I ran into it.
Okay, well, I can't get to that, unfortunately, but I do have a bomb and a key now.
So I could go get that item.
I've had this item before and I remember it being pretty good, but I don't remember what it is.
Oh yeah, this one is really good.
Way better than I remember.
That's amazing.
The sausage.
Love me some sausage.
I may go in here just to celebrate.
I kind of feel good about it now.
Hey, worth.
And pills galore.
Shot speed.
More shot speed.
Shot speed up.
Sure.
Oh my god.
And we get to leave without taking damage.
That was the best curse from of all time.
Oh my goodness.
Doesn't get better than that, guys.
Am I the chosen one?
Is it me?
Larry.
Oh god, I took damage.
Duplicate.
We gotta get rid of these poops.
Dude, come up here.
Binky is nice.
That's a buffer for the next floor.
Yeah.
The goal of this run is...
I guess we're gonna...
Yeah, we're gonna go home, I guess.
That's like the standard goal.
And if we don't get the teleport card, then we set a different goal.
This is like the standard setup for goals.
I'm so fast.
No, I took damage, but it's okay.
I had a buffer.
Run!
Dude, why is it so hard?
Why am I so fast?
Like, I was not this fast in the last floor, even though I got the belt.
Something's off.
I don't like that.
I could optimize this maybe and come back in case I find...
Oh, but then again, I guess I can duplicate it with my box.
If I get flies, right?
That's maybe not too bad.
If I do it correctly.
Dude, this is so scary.
Why is...
What's happening?
Why am I actually moving so fast?
Oh god!
This is crazy.
See?
You.
Nice.
I could have probably used the box here.
Would have been smart, I guess.
I need to find the boss, Asap, and kill it.
Okay, I'm scared.
Why did I go in the corner?
Get out.
Oi, oi, oi.
You have pretty crazy shot speed, man.
Those pills really...
Helped me a lot there.
I'm not going to risk this, honestly.
I don't trust my skills.
Not before we do the boss, at least.
What's that?
Demon's tail.
Aiders don't drop hearts or replace with the keys.
Oh, but all heart drops become black hearts.
Whoa!
I think I may like that.
Yeah.
Probably should have used this while picking that up before I, you know, but okay.
Duke of Flies.
That was actually surprisingly easy.
More tears is huge for me.
We're going to Angel.
I have decided so.
It is Angel.
I will say though, Angels are just in jail.
Oh, if I get these, I'm gonna...
Shit!
I'm just gonna say I'm gonna have 15 coins then.
But now I lost my black heart, so.
It's better have been worth it.
Let's see.
Doesn't look good, honestly.
Now we roll.
No!
Oh!
Actually sick.
I needed that.
Yeah.
Kind of want to bomb this.
We can hit all three with this.
I'll take this.
We got a couple buffers.
Not bad.
Let's leave.
I'm ready.
Go, go, go.
Third floor.
Flotted caves.
Oh, we have a dice room.
Maybe I'll come back for that after we deal with the boss.
Right now it's all about Angels.
Dude, I'm a machine gun right now.
I heard the meh.
Again, off to the side.
I don't know what's happening with that.
Ooh, black heart!
Now we need bombs.
Whoa!
The mulligan.
Dude, okay, I need bombs.
I need bombs here.
Oh, shit.
Come on, please grant me bombs.
These are good too, but...
Yo, listen!
Plus one luck.
Fly familiar that wanders around the room and reveals the locations of tinted rocks.
That's actually kind of cool.
Show me, Navi.
Wait, did it show me?
Where are you going?
Right here?
It's looking.
Uh...
Huh?
Okay, I guess there's nothing.
Good.
Oh, I think it's revealing something.
But it's not gonna matter if I don't have any bombs.
Like bombs is an insane bottleneck for me right now.
Secret room, oh my goodness.
Fuck you.
Can't believe it.
Yeah, I have one bomb.
I think I'd rather save it, maybe.
Nah, do it.
Okay, the door is open in the distance.
But what about infinite bombs?
Can I have that instead?
I ran into that!
Because I'm so bad!
Bomb, sick.
I have mine.
This is gonna take me to two out of three on both Beelzebub and Spiderbaby.
For that alone, I think that's worth it.
We just gotta find the money.
We also have a Navi in here.
Oh, what the fuck, I didn't see you!
Didn't even see that guy!
Oh my goodness.
I can't open that chest in case there's spikes on it.
I'll be back.
Duplicate!
That should duplicate all my spiders, right?
Oh!
Okay, come on.
Don't get hit!
I hate this guy.
I hate this guy so much.
Whoa!
Please die.
Yes!
Huge!
No, man, give me plus HP!
This run is getting close to being over.
Nice!
He wants coins.
He's gonna give me batteries, so I don't think that's worth it.
Fuck him.
Ah!
Piss off!
Shit!
I hate when that happens so much!
It feels so incredibly bad.
Stupid arena.
I'm gonna die.
This is over.
Do we have healing anywhere?
No.
We have a black heart, actually.
I'm going back for that.
Yeah, this one as well.
No!
You're kidding!
I need another bomb for that?
Insane.
That is such a buzzkill.
Yeah, I mean, we have infinite keys, so...
Wait, hold on, five?
What is five?
Oh, restart current...
Oh!
That's actually...
kind of cool, actually.
But wait, before I do, I should probably grab...
I need another bomb before I do that.
I don't know what that does.
I need to do this.
What the fuck is that?
A bomb is sick.
Nice.
Up to four, uncollect the pick-ups from the previous floor were spawned in the starting room of a new floor.
Wait, so how does that work if I restart?
I'm actually so curious.
Hold on.
A treasure room will appear in the womb and corpse floors.
That's also nice.
But I think I'll take this and try this.
This is too...
This is too interesting.
I'm gonna take this.
I'm gonna go back and grab this thing.
There you go.
We're actually not done on this floor either.
There's more.
Let me see.
Aha, okay.
Not exciting.
I wonder if restarting the floor also restarts me with full HP.
It's like the hourglass, you know?
I could...
No, let's not do that.
Yeah, I think we're good.
We're gonna leave.
What I mean is we're gonna try and restart.
This is exciting.
Here we go.
Third floor again.
Okay.
We did not...
Oh!
Oh, okay.
I thought it would give me all the stuff from the shop as well.
Because it's technically not picked up.
Okay.
Wait, let me read this again.
Up to four uncollected pickups from the previous floor will spawn in the starting...
Oh, I guess it's up to four.
So it's just randomly chose this, I guess.
Um, I guess I don't need to wear...
I'll keep this for now.
Wait, really?
Five again?
Can we just keep doing this?
There's no fucking way.
We're gonna definitely try that.
But I need to explore first.
Come on.
35% angel chance, by the way.
So maybe we get another shot at angel room.
Oh, wait, this is a...
Mercurius.
Speed?
Oh, we're gonna have almost max speed then.
Most doors remain open in rooms with enemies.
In fact, does not apply to boss room doors or ones that require a key to open.
Cool.
And what is that one?
Eowas?
That's nice.
I like that.
And hagalas.
Very cool.
Man, I wish they would use the music for that room in different places, because it's so nice.
And you're not in there for long, you know?
Okay, we got one bomb.
If I do this right, check it out.
I can get to both the key and the secret.
Galaxy brain.
I need more bombs.
Oh, that's a...
Is that a floor decoration?
I don't trust it, man.
Look for floor decorations.
Maybe in here.
It must be, right?
It was like a piece of paper.
It had to be.
And again, it's not really a decoration on the floor.
It's like a piece of paper, so...
Oh, there you are.
20 gold.
A freaking Bible in here?
Have I ever seen that in a shop?
I feel like that's new.
Uh,
mine is tears.
I kind of want to...
But then again, I need my box.
My box is kind of the whole point.
I think I'm going to donate.
I've been doing so much donating today.
It's kind of sick.
Not today, sir.
We got something in here.
Secret room.
Red patch.
Told me there was a chance to get a damage up for the current room.
Each time I take damage.
Wait, I don't have a bomb!
Fuck me, dude.
Also, I need to look for this AWAS situation.
The AWAS is going crazy right now.
Okay, I may just have to...
Wait, what was that piece of paper I saw?
Oh, nice.
Bomb?
Huge.
It was here, right?
Okay, let's just try it.
Nice!
Okay, piece of paper confirmed.
Works.
Little larva.
That's right, poop spawn a blue attack fly.
It's a trinket, though.
No, thanks.
We got a bit of extra money there.
I could go back and buy that blue heart before I engage the boss, just for extra security.
We have 35% angel chance.
It's not a lot, but it's not bad either, you know?
Well, I could also get...
I can potentially...
No, get this one.
And then...
It's time...
Oh, treasure room!
What the frick?
I completely forgot about the treasure room.
Oh, what a shit item.
Well, now we can get the other heart.
That's something.
Let's go.
We do the boss now, and then we're potentially gonna reset.
Uh, yeah.
There's nothing else I wanna do, right?
Oh, maybe this, actually.
Damn.
No money left.
Mega fatty.
Oh, I also have two navies.
Check that out.
Nice.
Finally some HP up.
That's good.
I'm gonna go back now.
And maybe...
Oh, you know what?
Let's head into the curse room.
Wait, I'm gonna take this again.
Before I do, uh...
Yeah, you know what I mean.
Holy shit!
Blue, uh, black hearts galore.
Amazing.
Now we're taking this.
We're gonna go in here.
There's nothing else I need to do, right?
Oh, we have a hagalas, actually.
Let's pick that up.
I could use that in here.
Damn.
Too bad.
All right, let's go.
Uh, are we ready?
Let me see checklist.
Check, check, check.
No money.
Check.
Okay, go.
This is so fucked!
Third floor again!
Here we go again!
And I get to...
Hey, I'll take this, though.
Uh, I'm gonna go in here immediately.
This is a shit curse room.
Boo.
Wait, now I have, uh, two familiars.
Like, yeah, it is totally like a thing where, after a certain amount of floors, you just get it.
But the funny thing is, I'm still on third floor.
So, I guess it counts as moving on, even though I'm not moving on.
Reveals the map, I love it!
Great.
Why am I lacking bombs so freakin' much in this run?
Yeah, I need a bomb here.
Let's go to the treasure room.
It feels like I'm flying, but I'm not.
It's just because I'm so fast, you know?
We can also go step, potentially, but with a bunch of black hearts, maybe not the greatest idea.
Uh, ooh, what is that?
Angry fly!
He's violent!
Okay.
Or, oh, Beelzebub has been...
What does that do?
Whoops, I...
What happened?
Why did it become...
Guys, what did I click?
Hold on, I'm gonna...
What did I do?
Uh, hold on.
F, okay, thanks.
Wait, no, no, open.
That's such a stupid keybind.
Who would ever do that?
Why would you wanna make it small?
Like, horrible.
Okay, let me read this again.
We got Beelzebub.
Uh,
I'm not sure what it did.
Oh, we're flying!
Note it down.
Beelzebub.
Three out of three is flight as well.
So many things are just flight.
That's awesome.
Well, now I really do fly.
Kind of funny that I mentioned the flying thing just before this happened.
You heard that?
The meh sound was there again.
Okay, uh, still no bomb, which is insane.
I don't freaking believe it.
I know there's a secret.
I can't get it.
I'll have to buy bombs.
Okay, there's a bomb.
Nice, two bombs!
Huge, two bombs more, yo!
We are so back.
This is exactly what I needed.
More, oh my god, we're being showered with bombs now.
This is the best thing ever for me.
Okay, that's fine.
13 coins.
We can get a bigger buffer.
It's actually not a bad idea.
Mom's pills.
Cards.
Could buy another bomb.
Let's keep donating.
I have been doing such a good job with that today.
$6.99.
We even get luck from that.
I actually forgot that was a thing.
I did remember now that I saw that earlier, but I totally forgot.
Okay, here we go.
We have a huge buffer.
This should be easy.
Gurdie Jr.
Wow, he died fast.
No chance.
Crackjacks.
What's that?
Gigante Bean?
No, thanks.
I'm good.
We could go step potentially.
No, wait, wait, hold on.
Wait a minute.
Zero coins.
Six bombs.
I could look for the other secret room, actually.
Go down here.
Show me the good stuff.
So I wonder how...
Maybe there's like a thing where if you sacrifice a black heart for this, you know, you trade a black heart.
Maybe I have a higher chance of getting something good out of this.
This is an experiment.
First one gave a coin.
Another coin.
Okay, I don't think so.
We're gonna move on.
I was hoping maybe an angel would immediately appear, you know?
Or something like that.
But it doesn't seem to be the case.
So whatever.
This guy, I'm gonna blow him up.
Sick.
Dude, I love this fucking trinket.
This is actually insane.
This may be one of the best trinkets.
Oh, wait.
Hey, I forgot we had an RV for this.
A blue heart, come on, man.
I only deal in black hearts nowadays.
Kind of want to go back and step again.
That's right.
Yeah, you know what?
Yes, I believe.
We're gonna step again, baby.
I'm doing it.
You can't stop me.
You may think I'm loco in the moco, but it is what it is.
A pill.
It's gonna be HP up.
Maybe.
I feel blessed.
Whatever that means.
Scapular.
What was that again?
When damage down to the last half heart, automatically gain one soul heart.
I mean, sure.
Whatever.
I'm gonna blow this guy up now.
Sup, fool.
You're not gonna do any lasers or something.
Key piece for me.
Vibrant bulb.
No, that one is not super interesting to me.
It's fine.
Do I have any hearts lying around?
Doesn't look like it, so we're not gonna step anymore.
Now, the bad thing about this, it was a trade.
But we're not gonna have a buffer now for the next floor.
But it's okay.
All things considered, we had a couple extra floors on floor three.
So I think we can survive even without it.
Caves two.
71% angel.
Let's really try not to get hit, huh?
Really utilize the fact that we can fly.
Don't forget about that now.
Speed up, H.
Ah, man!
It's looking bleak now all of a sudden.
Shit.
That was a bad pill.
Real bad pill.
The good news is, we still have the trinket that gives us black hearts, so we should be finding something at some point.
Did you get a buffer?
I'm so scared.
Oh, the red one is mine.
Fuck, I keep thinking it's an enemy.
Oh, shit!
Oh, god!
Okay.
Dutch!
Holy shit.
Buffer, buffer detected.
And money detected.
Wow.
Thank you.
Uh, I could also buy a bomb.
Wait, how do I have three hearts again?
Oh, no, wait.
I had four and I went to three, right?
That's how that works.
Okay.
So far, so good.
Nah, nah, nah, nah, you can't reach me.
Fuck you.
Almost fell for that one.
I'll be back for you later.
Ah!
Nice.
Acid bay- oh.
That drops a pill every seven rooms.
That's actually kind of nice.
Let's do some acid.
Not bad.
Also duplicated, right?
When I use my box.
My box of secrets.
Secret in here.
Thank you, Navi.
Could be good.
Umbilical cord.
Nah.
Come on, man.
Something!
Oh my god, really?
I got robbed!
Never mind.
We're back.
Keep gambling.
This has not been worth it.
Okay.
No!
Unbelievable!
I have been robbed.
More than ever before.
Ah-ha!
Not falling for that!
Bastard.
Okay, I'm gonna blow you up.
Plus one luck!
What happened there?
Oh, right.
He does damage to everyone in the room because I have the acid baby.
Don't spike me.
Bad trip.
No thanks.
Wait, turns into a full health pill when at one health.
That's actually something I need to keep in mind.
Could be useful later in this run.
And we have arrived with equality.
Grants and large fire rate increase when collected.
Coins, bombs, and...
Wait.
I mean, is there any reason not to take this?
Oh, it's a trinket.
That's why.
We have one buffer.
Let's go!
This should be okay.
I'm gonna multiply and destroy it.
Very sick.
Plus one health.
Love it.
We're gonna get angels now.
Ooh, that one's good!
Spear of Destiny.
No, this one.
Absolutely that one.
That one is incredible.
Blow him up.
Fight me, nerd!
Oh, what the hell is that?
Kind of angel baby.
Yo, yes, he has a lot of HP here.
My damage is not that good.
Mmm, could try and...
Oh, pill.
Sick!
Finally!
Very nice.
I feel so good.
I'm gonna go to the curse room.
Especially with the mantle.
The mantle shall guide me.
Also, we can do this now.
But let's do this first.
We're gonna walk through these rooms anyway.
We're gonna have to give up that blue heart we have.
Wait, goat head?
But this is devil deals.
Does that work with angels?
Wait, it gave me a lot of angel chances.
Oh?
All right.
Oh, wait a- Oh my god, I keep forgetting.
The mantle is every...
Uh, room!
I thought it was for one floor.
This thing is insane.
Wait, I can just go- Dude.
Hold on a minute.
If there was a step room...
...there's no way, right?
I can just go back in and out?
That thing's broken.
There's no way that's possible.
Cursed skull.
Damage to half a heart remaining.
Isaac instalutes it.
What is it with these items that does something when I reach half a heart?
It's been every single floor so far.
I've been- I'm finding three of these so far, I think.
Like, I'm not gonna get to half a heart because I'm a gamer.
Those items are useless to me.
Nice!
We can look for secrets.
We got five bombs.
I think I see one.
No, I don't.
Maybe up here.
Well, we already found one secret anyway, so fuck it.
Let's pick up the chests here.
Am I glad I saved those chests for later?
Where else can I abuse this mantle?
I don't know.
Yeah, this one stays open.
Look.
Not worth it.
Okay, fine.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Okay, dank depths.
Another bat trip.
What is it with those?
Oh, that was a secret in there.
Wait, I can just walk back?
That's right.
Now I know what's in there.
So they're gonna do lasers, most likely.
Fight room.
Nice.
That was a good chest.
These things are gonna randomly charge across the room.
Wait, what happened?
That was weird.
Plus one lock.
Insane.
Dude, I have nine luck?
I mean, that's gotta do something.
We really need to pay attention to what luck effects in this run.
Like, something big has got to change now.
You destroyed my mantle.
Another luck!
Ten luck, baby!
Luckiest girl on Earth.
Ooh, I could...
Wait.
No fucking way.
Ah, wait.
Okay, maybe that doesn't work like that.
That would have been broken.
Okay, okay.
I understand.
I get it.
This guy's really annoying.
Please get away.
Kill him!
Oh my god.
Are you serious?
Finally.
What was that?
Kill this guy.
Gonna jump at me or something?
No!
This room is chaos!
That was tough.
Cricket's body?
Plus half a tear.
Less range.
Tears split into four half dead.
That's actually pretty good.
I've had this before.
It's good for AOE.
No, thanks.
We found one secret.
Oh yeah, we are actually guaranteed to find all secrets, really.
Because of Na'Vi.
Hey, listen!
All right.
Yeah, we got a secret in here.
Wait, there's something there?
You found something, boy?
Oh.
All right.
I was hoping it was gonna be a hatch.
Downstairs.
Sweet.
Oh, champion belt!
I love that item.
A great item.
I'm gonna donate the rest.
Because I'm such a good guy.
We gained a lot of Angel as well there.
Showed just in time!
Wow, that went far.
He dead, though.
The boss from his item, I don't know how to find the right eye.
Perfect.
Just that.
Circle of protection.
Ah, sure.
And now fight me.
Amazing.
Wait, there's something in here?
Na'Vi?
No way.
Hold on.
No.
No, no, no.
Not happening.
This one was spawn a puddle of slippery.
I mean, I may as well take it.
It's good for me.
Now I just need spectral tears.
And then we are really cooking.
Somehow I'm hitting them still.
Ah, what's this?
Oh.
With 10 luck?
Come on.
Okay, you know what?
We have confirmed, without a doubt, luck does not affect these machines.
Because with 10 luck, we would have seen something here.
Like a much higher rate of luck.
You know?
Chance of fire, poison tears, chance increases with luck.
That is actually...
not doing anything!
Because that's only on my character, it seems.
You see that?
There's no poison tears here.
That sucks.
So all my luck is wasted, I guess.
That feels so bad.
Also, there's a pill up here.
Bad trip.
Paperclip, no thanks.
I may actually go step and remove all of my buffers again.
Because I'm a psycho.
Nah!
Once per run, psycho move is probably fine.
No more.
This is empty, let's go!
Now it's mom!
Mom, mom, mom, we need a teleport card!
Otherwise, all dreams are gone.
This is our must-have right now.
Let's see if we can't find that, huh?
Shit.
Had to have.
Nothing.
Oh my god.
I mean, okay, here we go!
I'll come back for that, maybe.
But that means we won't be able to enter the boss room, right?
God damn it.
Well, I have 23 anyway, so...
I see it, Navi.
I'm coming.
Blank card.
Triggers the effect of the card without...
Maybe good.
Depends on if we'll find a card.
That is good, right?
This is always fun.
Some stats...
I think this, yeah.
I think I like that.
Less speed on my shots, though, is a little bit painful, but it's not too bad.
Haven't found a shop yet.
So we should...
Also, we should not enter there, by the way.
Just saying.
I was, like, briefly considering that.
I mean, I guess we'll...
I can't afford it, never mind.
There's that pill.
Kind of want to get that.
Pretty fly.
Let's keep moving.
Give me that money.
Terrible curse room, again.
South.
Nice!
I mean, I'm just kind of cleaning house right now.
What do we have here?
Wait, that was bad, I think.
One is bad.
One, one, one.
Reroll all items!
Yeah, no.
No.
Oh, that's cool.
No, thank you.
Again, Mom?
What was that?
Oh, what the hell?
That's so...
Oh, there's a secret in here.
Okay, it's fine.
We got the mantle.
Damn, he died fast.
Sick HP up.
That's huge up.
Very nice.
Okay.
What am I looking for now?
We still have a fight room, but I think that's closed.
And one more secret left.
Oh, wait, there was a secret here.
Where was it?
Tell me, Navi.
Here.
Yeah.
Man, I'm getting all this shit that I can't really use.
I think I'm gonna donate this money.
We're gonna donate the money.
First, check, fight club, donate money, and then...
Then we head in here, because we haven't found a teleport card.
It's sad as hell.
It's closed.
Shit.
Oh, wait, we need the thing for that, which is over here.
Polaroid.
We're gonna open the door, come back for the other one.
Boink!
Look at the way we put it inside.
Did you see that?
So dope.
Uh, there.
Wait, there's something on the map still, though.
Like, what is that?
No, the one on the right side.
Oh, it was the thing that I just saw, okay.
All right, I'm just a little confused right now.
Just wanna double check things before I leave.
I think everything's cool.
We go.
And this time, we're not gonna step our way into another dimension.
We're doing it.
All right.
So did that bomb explode, or did it not?
I saw the animation, briefly.
It's a question for the philosophers.
Let's see.
It did explode.
My damage is pretty good.
More lock?
Sure, why not?
To the nail?
Every six seconds, transforms into a- Oh, wait, this is the funny one!
And in this statue form, Isaac is invincible to most forms of damage.
Man, I need this.
I need to do it.
Let's listen.
Yes!
This will fuel me.
Nice.
Oh, champion!
Uh, I can't see what it is, I'm not gonna risk it yet.
Oh, wait, my little red flies are just killing things!
If I can just stand here and wait, or...
That's kind of crazy.
Oh, he's not going for it, or...
No, let me grab the coin.
What now?
Bad trip, shit.
Okay, good thing I didn't use that.
Oh, wow.
Airpin.
Fully charges Isaac's active item when entering a new boss room.
That's a trinket, though.
Yeah.
No thanks.
I like my current trinkets.
Oh, shop speed!
That's actually so nice, I needed that.
Tarot card, we don't know what that is.
What's that one?
Sponsor coins when taking damage.
Mayus...
No, that's too late for that.
Way too late.
I'm gonna donate money, I think.
Buy this one.
Justice?
Wait, what was that?
Oh, spawn some things.
Get that one.
Uh, and we're gonna donate the rest.
Boom.
I have donated so much!
The procorice is off the charts.
Okay, time to go down again.
This is the minus tiers.
Oh yeah, man, shop speed is back on top here.
Feels much better.
Wait a minute, the mantle goes beyond the max hearts!
Whoa!
That's kind of sick!
We got a secret in here.
More range?
I'm actually gonna give this guy some H.
Nah, I'll be back, maybe.
Uh, blow that up.
And that one.
More range?
Oh, that's x-lax.
Nope!
What the...
Dark prince's crown.
While at one red heart, the crown activates and gives plus two fire rate plus range.
That's actually not bad.
This one's also nice.
Oh my god, I kind of want to buy it all!
Is that illegal?
Wait, wait, wait.
Let me get rid of this first.
Okay, I'm buying it all.
I'm taking...
Because I can take my hearts down.
Get that one.
Oh yeah, baby.
Insanity.
And then we had a place where we could donate back here.
But before we do that, we need to establish some ground rules here.
Meaning we need a buffer before we do that.
Otherwise, it's too risky.
Curse of the tower.
Nah, I'm good.
Oh wait, there was a secret somewhere that I forgot.
Oh no, I think I got it.
Okay.
Holy shit.
There goes my mantle.
Another X-lax.
Okay.
Secret.
Whoa, what the hell?
Buffers?
Guppy's head.
Ah, no.
I mean, I'll use it once.
May as well, right?
More spiders.
Aw, man.
Okay.
Uh, I think we may want to go in now.
No, wait.
Not yet.
One last room.
I'm strongly considering taking my hearts down to one.
Well, that is extremely risky, actually.
I don't have a wafer, right?
So I can easily lose my buffers and then I'm fucked if that happens.
So I don't think it's a good idea.
I have good damage already.
So let's not risk it.
Yeah.
Time to leave.
Or go to the boss.
Oh!
Didn't mean to do that.
Guess we can do one more.
Yeah, that's fine.
Ah, blow them up.
I'll take a heart from here.
Ah, but wait.
Yeah, take it.
Uh, down.
Now we leave.
Wait, checklist.
Shop!
Uh, we could go back and donate.
But nah, you know what?
Fuck it, man.
I just want to go.
I'm going.
Here we go.
We spent it all on gambling.
Empty.
I need spectral tears.
I can barely see anything with all these guys following me.
Yeah, let's just go.
We're ascending.
Wow.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
Harkalas?
Uh, yeah.
Just go.
Shut up, man.
Shut up.
You just keep pushing me like this.
I'm leaving.
Leave.
We'll be fine without you.
Spoilers.
We were not fine without him.
Oh, my God.
Jim, Jim, Jim.
This guy's crazy.
Duppy's collar.
Oh, can't be revived.
That's sick.
One of the better guppy items.
Maybe I should explore every room on these floors, man.
Because if I hadn't done that, I wouldn't have gotten that item.
It's always worth it.
Oh, get up.
Why does it say X1?
Oh, I guess it can happen again.
But it's not guaranteed.
Oh, it means it's not guaranteed that it will ever happen.
That's why I question Mark.
What
was that?
Cheers down.
No, thanks.
Whoa.
Money, money, money.
Oh, there it is.
I thought he just blew up my black card.
Wait, where's the exits?
Oh, here.
Crack key!
We're gonna save it.
You are insane.
You are taking this too far.
More range.
I feel like these big boys here are kind of a nice measurement of how much damage I have.
It's like a damage test, you know?
Because they're so tanky.
It's a good way to gauge it.
This way.
Oh, nice.
They become my friends.
I'm gonna have an insane army.
If I kill enemies fast enough, you know, before they die, it's gonna be kind of funny to do the boss after this.
More shot speed!
Love that!
Okay, there's the exits.
Imagine duplicating them all as well.
The hell was that?
Oh, the tower.
Wait, where did my thing go?
Didn't I have a thing?
Where did my key go?
Oh, fly a little.
Why did I leave that?
Wait, what?
What happened?
The tower?
Why is it not showing up on the map?
I have no idea, dude.
Wow!
Look at that chest!
I mean, not that we need money, but, you know, it's just...
Oh, there it is.
Why does it show up as a card, though?
That's kind of confusing.
Less tears.
Look at all my flies!
I'm the Lord of Flies.
Okay, it's time we leave.
No, down.
Basement two.
I have a prediction.
I think this key is gonna open a different door in the home.
No, I don't want that.
Like somewhere else.
And I wonder if Navi is gonna point it out.
What do I need all this money for?
Oh, like, I guess I could roll the dice on this one.
Rainbow worm.
Wait, what's that?
What is that?
Why does it say what it is?
Huh?
What the fuck is that crap?
No effect?
Oh.
Yeah, why not?
Okay, maybe luck does affect this.
Because holy shit, we're getting a lot.
This is a very high success rate.
Maybe.
What the heck is that?
No, that's not needed.
It's only gonna spawn trinkets and see.
Okay, you know what, fuck it.
Pacifism.
I remember that room.
Oh!
Look at it!
What a boring one.
I've never seen that starfish guy.
Oh, shit.
What's that?
Plus one luck?
Sure, why not?
Keep giving me luck.
I'm excited!
We can leave.
Also, I miss my key.
There it is.
I'm gonna go left before I go down.
Look at all the flies.
Dude, when I duplicate this, you're gonna see some serious shit.
Ooh!
Not that that's doing much for me at this point.
Holy HP.
Petrified poop.
What's that one?
Strength was...
Well, nothing I can use right now.
Okay, I think we're good.
Take me.
Basement one.
Also, Navi has not pointed out anything in these floors.
Yes.
I'm kind of hoping it would potentially point out something new, you know?
Remember that one?
Remember that one.
Still not interested.
No, thanks.
I just wasted all my fucking familiars on these guys.
I like this one.
Speed.
Ex-lax, not interested in that.
Oh, wait.
Okay,
we can leave here.
Is that up?
That's cool.
Oh, what's that?
New floors will generate an additional secret room.
I don't think that's gonna work, though.
At this point, it's too late for that.
Okay, we got a little guy with us now.
What was that pill?
Oh, it was Ex-lax.
I think we're ready.
Keep going.
Here we go!
Time to fight the TV.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Look at this room.
Upside down cross, we got knives, pictures of demons, pictures of fat babies, and pentagrams.
It's different.
I'm looking for outlines.
Okay.
Okay, still doesn't do anything.
Ah!
There it is!
Uh, Q.
No more Eulith.
We have entered the Lilith Age.
Oh, wait, I need to open this.
Mom's awake.
Eul's a red heart.
Firing has a chance to spawn blue spiders.
Increases with luck!
We have a lot of luck.
Bro, we're gonna have impossibly many spiders, and I'm gonna duplicate it.
In fact, I'm gonna wait with duplicating until I have a million spiders.
Are you ready?
What's on TV?
It's dogma again.
Dude, I'm actually scared of using my active.
I want to save it for the next bosses.
I feel like I may have not, I may, I, I, no, use it, fuck.
It's okay, trust.
We're gonna get the energy.
Dude, I have good damage, holy shit!
Wow, you got smaaagged!
Here we go!
We don't have enough energy!
Oh no, I fucked up!
Hopefully we're gonna get more energy as we go on.
That is crazy.
Come on, energy, energy?
Yes!
I'm gonna save my energy.
No, use it.
Dude, I'm dealing a lot of damage here.
Holy shit, bro.
He's mad now.
Easy, easy.
Come on, give me a challenge!
What is this?
You're doing that, okay.
You're nothing.
Next!
You're done, son.
You're mine.
You're mine!
It gets sucked in, dude.
Next!
Dude, I fucking nailed that so hard.
Holy shit, I don't think I even took a hit during that.
I may be mistaken, but that was insane.
All right.
We also unlocked something.
I forgot what it...
Oh, oh, dude!
Lilith!
Fetal Fury.
Jello.
Also Windstreak of Two, by the way.
We're gonna check that out.
Next time.
Boom!
We gotta end it on that.
That was magnificent.
Guys, remember what I said in the last stream?
Meaning, if you were here to watch The Sims.
I said, the script was prepared for today.
Everything was polished.
It was win, win, win.
No lose.
We didn't lose a single time today.
Not only did we not even lose, we didn't even get hit.
I told you.
Wait, wait!
Still though, two runs?
Come on!
That was good, man.
It's a Windstreak of Two, yes, it is.
Oh, I feel so good, guys.
I feel incredible.
Next stream, Windstreak of Three, on top of the two we have right now.
Oh, man.
Oliver David, why are you neglecting your son, Isaac, and playing much more with The Sims?
I'll stream Sims in the next stream, and then we're gonna alternate back and forth a bit.
Because I gotta be honest, I've been thinking about The Sims since yesterday.
I am legitimately kinda addicted.
You used all your luck this time.
Next stream, Windstreak of Minus 10.
Well, you know, that's not true.
And I'll prove you wrong.
Solidifies Oliver as the best there, possibly over IP address.
No, I don't know what that means.
What do you think about R-Key item?
I think it sounds insane.
I think it is kinda good.
It's a good item.
Good script, your ride is really tired.
I know.
Worth it, though.
Plans here.
The VOD will be up soon, okay?
Within at least, like, two and a half hours, max.
And the VOD on YouTube is so much better than the one on Twitch, because it's 4K and it's, you know, no ads and all that.
Well, there is ads, but not the same amount, I guess.
Twitch is kinda crazy on that front.
Chat is also scripted.
Oh, sorry, I said too much.
No, that's part of the script, Goose.
You're doing great.
This is the part of the script where we try to convince people that it's not a script.
You know?
We have to maintain a level of believability.
I mean, pre-recorded, it is!
I mean, we did this a couple days ago, but it wouldn't be a couple days ago at this time.
Yeah, it would.
Was the script printed outside your window?
Maybe, Ghost.
Wait, are you trying to tell me that you've been the guy outside my window all this time?
How did you know?
Are you out there secretly printing in the night, in the dark?
Okay, maybe it's not you.
Need more time to memorize my lines?
You don't have to, just copy-paste them.
It's all in the script, man.
Are we at the moment where you'll gift me money in the script?
Uh, no, that's not yet.
That comes later.
How does your cat look?
You can check it out in the pet channel, on the Discord.
I post pictures there of Jackie.
Not too much recently, but there's definitely pictures of her in there.
It may even be pinned.
Yeah, there's a pinned one of Jackie in there.
You can check it out.
I'll try and post more.
I forgot my lines.
Can you remind me?
Let me check the script here.
Uh, it says here, you have to praise me about my skills three times.
You've only done it once.
You need two more.
And then you've done your part.
Have the spoilers with the pigeon mail arrived yet?
Not yet.
That's tomorrow.
Today we have the smoke signals.
People are trying to spoil me via smoke signals long range while I was shopping.
I know, it's crazy what people do nowadays.
My script only says beg pathetically for greed.
Oh shit.
Listen, the plan was to do greed, but the plan was also to keep it in three hours.
This was supposed to be like a three-ish hour stream.
Next time we do greed first thing.
Maybe even two greed runs.
Yeah, quick question.
You can answer me this.
If I do a greed run and I fail, will that fuck up my streak?
Or is it gonna add to the streak as well?
Okay, it will fuck it up, but if I win, it'll be three in streak, right?
So that's good, because I feel like greed is easier than not greed.
So we're actually gonna get almost guaranteed to three, I think.
Nice, beautiful.
My script is to glaze over until I die.
I love that term glaze.
I'm just imagining someone putting like frosting on someone else, you know, while they're smiling.
Greed being main run is weird to me.
What do you mean?
Asasal glaze is glassasal.
I like that one.
Oh, maybe we'll do the new Lilith next time.
Exactly, Dr. Beant.
That's a good idea.
That's a perfect way to test that character.
Beautiful, great idea.
Let me write it down.
We do greed plus new Lilith.
Actually, it's just Lilith.
There's nothing new about it.
We had Eulith, now it's Lilith.
Nice.
That character's so cool.
Okay, I'm looking forward to it then.
I have high hopes.
I mean, I also want to try the other new characters I unlocked and more.
Like, I want to play the new Asasal as well.
Because that one is so good.
And the one that goes k-k-k-king, ching-ching, you know.
With the sword.
Now, let's see what you said.
Should be alternate mode like challenge.
But the game considers it being a main run.
Ah, I see what you mean, yeah.
I would actually agree with that.
I think it's weird that it's part of the difficulty slider and not part of a separate option in the menu.
I totally agree.
I think they should have done that.
Like normal mode and greed mode.
Then you go into that and you can choose difficulties within those two.
That would make more sense.
Doesn't quite make sense that greed is a difficulty mode, you know?
What about Isaac?
He still has only one or a mark.
Are we talking about the achievements?
The marks on the piece of paper?
Because, yeah, definitely I want to get more of those.
I want to get all the marks.
I guess that's kind of a nice long-range or long-term goal, you know?
Because at some point, I mean, it is a roguelike game.
But it's nice to have goals like that.
So I can look at the characters and go, oh, I still need to do that on that character or, you know?
Mark maxing?
Yes, exactly.
Colloquially clear marks.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, that makes sense, I guess.
Since you cleared that part of the game.
You should also make it so you can press G for greed.
Like you can press E for yulch at the characters.
G game, I think you should, you know, get off the bottle.
I think, are you okay right now?
You're slurring your words.
They're called completion marks.
I mean, that, I mean, whatever.
The idea is the same, right?
You get a mark, you get an achievement for doing one part of the game.
Completion marks, okay.
I mean, we could just call it that.
That's fine.
Elith Isasil Yudas.
Imagine a challenge where I have to say every word that I say in a stream with the letter E as the start.
So every sentence needs to start with an E.
And all words in that sentence.
And if I fail once during the stream, I get beaten with a stick in real life.
My feet, you know, someone is like on my feet and like bamboo.
Would that be entertaining?
I'm just imagining that.
And someone live streaming that with like a foot cam.
And then every time it happens, he kind of enjoys it too, you know?
So he goes like...
Every time.
And it just gets wilder and wilder as time goes on.
I would watch that.
Anyway, guys, I need to go.
I think I've cornered myself a little bit with that.
I'm leaving.
Thank you for watching.
I've been your host.
I'm Oliver.
I'm a god gamer.
I only win.
Don't forget it.
Next time, more wins.
Boom.
I'll see you around.
Bye-bye.